An Inventory of the Richard B. Foster papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Stanford Research Institute and SRI International reports, 1959-1987
  - U.S.-USSR joint working group in the the application of computers to management, 1980 (Box-folder 28: 4)
  - Computer-assisted strategic analysis, 1971 (Box-folder 28: 5)
  - Introduction to programs OPSTRA3 and OPSTRA5, 1971 (Box-folder 28: 6)
  - Sub-program HARDAT (Hard Site Attack), 1971 (Box-folder 28: 7)
  - Denial strategy, 1971 (Box-folder 28: 8)
  - Analysis of sufficiency criteria, 1971 (Box-folder 28: 9)
  - Soviet military doctrine, 1971 (Box-folder 29: 1-2)
  - Military strategy, 1971 (Box-folder 29: 3)
  - Overall balance of power in the 1970s, 1971 (Box-folder 29: 4)
  - Strategic systems effectiveness evaluation models, 1971 (Box-folder 29: 5)
  - Description of program OPSTRAS, 1971 (Box-folder 29: 6)
  - Alternative Soviet foreign policies, 1971 (Box-folder 29: 7)
  - Soviet-American interactions, 1971 (Box-folder 29: 8)
  - Army's contributions to national security, 1971 (Box-folder 29: 9)
  - Soviet perception of the Sino-Soviet conflict, 1971 (Box-folder 29: 10)
  - Theoretical aspects of comparing economic activity, 1972 (Box-folder 30: 1)
  - USSR expenditures for national security programs, 1971 (Box-folder 30: 2)
  - Comparison of U.S./USSR GNP, 1972 (Box-folder 30: 3)
  - U.S. industry funded RDT&E (Research Development Test and Evaluation), 1972 (Box-folder 30: 4)
  - U.S. Gross National Product, 1972 (Box-folder 30: 5)
  - Ruble/dollar conversion ratio survey, 1972 (Box-folder 30: 6)
  - Methodology for force posture research and study, 1971 (Box-folder 30: 7)
  - U.S. industry support for applied R&D, 1972 (Box-folder 30: 8)
  - Implications of the Nixon doctrine for the defense planning process, 1972 (Box-folder 30: 9)
  - Analysis of selected U.S. strategic force modifiers, 1972 (Box-folder 30: 10)
  - Legal considerations and constraints on U.S. nuclear policy, 1972 (Box-folder 30: 11)
  - Selections from the Soviet military press, 1973 (Box-folder 31: 1)
  - Integrated global force postures, 1973 (Box-folder 31: 2)
  - Dynamic interaction model of the Nixon doctrine, 1973 (Box-folder 31: 3)
  - War termination concepts, 1973 (Box-folder 31: 4)
  - War termination concepts, 1973 (Box-folder 31: 4)
  - Theater force posture analysis, 1973 (Box-folder 31: 5-6)
  - Input substudies, 1972 (Box-folder 31: 7)
  - Analysis of the U.S. and USSR potential for economic recovery, 1972 (Box-folder 31: 8)
  - Overview of the citizen-army concept, 1972 (Box-folder 31: 9)
  - Possible patterns of nuclear proliferation, 1974 (Box-folder 31: 10)
  - Yugoslav concept of general people's defense, 1972 (Box-folder 31: 11)
  - Wars of national liberation, 1972 (Box-folder 32: 1)
  - Communist China's trade patterns, 1974 (Box-folder 32: 2)
  - Input to STRATOP(Strategic Operations)-83, 1971 (Box-folder 32: 3-10)
  - SALT (Strategic Arms Limitation Talks) and U.S. strategic options, 1971 (Box-folder 32: 11)
  - Observations on SALT, 1971 (Box-folder 32: 12)
  - Relationships between strategic and general purpose forces, 1971 (Box-folder 32: 13)
  - Army's contributions to national security policy-making, 1971 (Box-folder 32: 14)
  - Report on a flying trip to Europe, 1971 (Box-folder 32: 15)
  - Soviet foreign policy and the collapse of communist unity, 1971 (Box-folder 32: 16)
  - Changing concept of deterrence, 1971 (Box-folder 32: 17)
  - Asian trip report, 1971 (Box-folder 32: 18)
  - Political/military uncertainties, 1971 (Box-folder 32: 19)
  - Notes on the global balance of power, 1971 (Box-folder 32: 20)
  - Political leadership crisis in Poland, 1971 (Box-folder 32: 21)
  - Soviet field command structure, 1971 (Box-folder 32: 22)
  - Twenty-fourth congress of CPSU and SALT, 1971 (Box-folder 32: 23)
  - Methodological features of the X-66 study, 1971 (Box-folder 32: 24)
  - Preliminary observations on strategic interactions, 1971 (Box-folder 32: 25)
  - Overview of the methodology for force posture research and study, 1971 (Box-folder 32: 26)
  - Analysis of damage level measurement criteria, 1971 (Box-folder 32: 27)
  - U.S. strategic force objectives and SALT, 1972 (Box-folder 33: 1)
  - Soviet objectives at SALT II, 1972 (Box-folder 33: 2)
  - Pitfalls in SALT II, 1972 (Box-folder 33: 3)
  - U.S. policy objectives in SALT II, 1972 (Box-folder 33: 4)
  - U.S. and Soviet objectives in SALT II, 1972 (Box-folder 33: 5)
  - Negotiations and arms conrol in Europe, 1972 (Box-folder 33: 6)
  - Briefing on the issues of tactical nuclear weapons, 1973 (Box-folder 33: 7)
  - U.S. restraints on nuclear data sharing, 1971 (Box-folder 33: 8)
  - Nixon doctrine and the Indian Ocean, 1971 (Box-folder 33: 9)
  - Implications of the Nixon doctrine for military policy, 1971 (Box-folder 33: 10)
  - Political and military implications of the Nixon doctrine for Europe, 1971 (Box-folder 33: 11)
  - Nixon doctrine and sub-Saharan Africa, 1971 (Box-folder 33: 12)
  - Wars of national liberation in the 1970s, 1971 (Box-folder 33: 13)
  - Policy analysis in relation to the emerging world order, 1971 (Box-folder 33: 14)
  - USSR expenditures for science, 1972 (Box-folder 33: 15)
  - Role of U.S. overseas bases, 1972 (Box-folder 33: 16)
  - Theater forces study, 1972 (Box-folder 33: 17)
  - Visit to the Soviet Union, 1972 (Box-folder 33: 18)
  - Supporting research for force posture analysis, 1972 (Box-folder 33: 19)
  - Mission and function of major U.S. Army combat units, 1972 (Box-folder 33: 20)
  - Table of organization and equipment for selected U.S. Army combat units, 1972 (Box-folder 33: 21)
  - Dialectics of post-SALT U.S.-USSR relations, 1972 (Box-folder 33: 22)
  - Negotiations and arms control in Europe, 1972 (Box-folder 33: 22)
  - Communications traffic in conflict situations, 1962 (Box-folder 34: 1)
  - Communications requirements for tension situations and limited war, 1962 (Box-folder 34: 2)
  - Speed of communications, precedence, and traffic control, 1962 (Box-folder 34: 3)
  - Continuity of government in general nuclear war, 1962 (Box-folder 34: 4)
  - Command control communications program, 1963 (Box-folder 34: 5)
  - Applicable technology for army command, control, and communications, 1983 (Box-folder 34: 6)
  - National goals and survival measures, 1980 (Box-folder 35: 1)
  - National strategic command-control-communications requirements, 1962 (Box-folder 35: 2)
  - Basic issues connected with national command, control, and communications, 1981 (Box-folder 35: 3)
  - National emergency operations planning, 1973 (Box-folder 35: 4)
  - Contingency planning documents for multipurpose staging areas, 1973 (Box-folder 35: 5)
  - Contingency planning documents for shelter complexes, 1973 (Box-folder 35: 6)
  - Long term strategic forecast for the Republic of China, 1980 (Box-folder 35: 7)
  - Negotiations and arms control in Europe, 1972 (Box-folder 35: 8)
  - Influence of NATO/Europe on Soviet military policy, 1970 (Box-folder 35: 9)
  - International legal parameters of nuclear policy and planning, 1973 (Box-folder 35: 10)
  - Nixon doctrine, 1973 (Box-folder 35: 11)
  - Implications of the Nixon doctrine for American international negotiation, 1973 (Box-folder 35: 12-13)
  - American approaches to international negotiation, 1973 (Box-folder 35: 14)
  - Emerging U.S. global strategy, 1973 (Box-folder 35: 15)
  - Iran: an emerging power, 1976 (Box-folder 36: 1)
  - Role of U.S.-Soviet trade in Soviet growth strategy, 1976 (Box-folder 36: 2)
  - Soviet economic problems, 1979 (Box-folder 36: 3)
  - Limited mobilization, 1980 (Box-folder 36: 4)
  - National telecommunications system strategic planning, 1981 (Box-folder 36: 5)
  - Training and utilization of scientists and engineers, 1981 (Box-folder 36: 6)
  - Education and employment of scientists and engineers, 1981 (Box-folder 36: 7)
  - Prolonged war in Soviet strategy, 1981 (Box-folder 36: 8)
  - Regulatory impacts on national security telecommunications, 1981 (Box-folder 36: 9)
  - Framework for national communications system strategic planning, 1982 (Box-folder 36: 10)
  - U.S. security interests in Central America, 1983 (Box-folder 36: 11)
  - The science race, 1981 (Box-folder 36: 12)
  - Ten per cent reduction for MBFR in Europe, 1973 (Box-folder 36: 13)
  - Taiwan: a state in transition, 1973 (Box-folder 36: 14)
  - Military procurement in the Soviet Union, 1973 (Box-folder 36: 15)
  - Emergence of a European defense research institute, 1974 (Box-folder 36: 17)
  - Trip report to the Soviet Union, 1973 (Box-folder 36: 16)
  - Technology transfer to Russia, 1974 (Box-folder 37: 1)
  - Lessons learned about the USSR, 1974 (Box-folder 37: 2)
  - An American view of economic relations with the USSR, 1974 (Box-folder 37: 3)
  - Observations on American-Soviet trade, 1974 (Box-folder 37: 4)
  - Soviet economic performance in 1973, 1974 (Box-folder 37: 5)
  - Observations on Soviet defense expenditures, 1975 (Box-folder 37: 6)
  - Soviet economic performance in 1974, 1975 (Box-folder 37: 7)
  - U.S./USSR defense expenditure comparisons, 1975 (Box-folder 37: 8)
  - Research design, 1975 (Box-folder 37: 9)
  - Far East trip report, 1975 (Box-folder 37: 11)
  - Public-private policy issues, 1976 (Box-folder 37: 12)
  - Observations on the world mineral availability problem, 1975 (Box-folder 37: 13)
  - Economic relations with the West in Soviet economic strategy, 1976 (Box-folder 37: 14)
  - Substance of comparative strategy, 1978 (Box-folder 37: 15)
  - Interest groups and influence in the defense policymaking process, 1976 (Box-folder 37: 16)
  - War and emergency powers in the United States, 1976 (Box-folder 37: 17)
  - Strategic utility of Patriot deployment, 1979 (Box-folder 37: 18)
  - Indicators of political instability in less developed countries, 1980 (Box-folder 37: 19)
  - Continuity of government for national entity survival, 1980 (Box-folder 37: 20)
  - System engineering and technical assistance, 1981 (Box-folder 37: 21)
  - Strategic framework for arms control, 1981 (Box-folder 38: 1-2)
  - NCS (National Communications System) joint government-industry network planning, 1981 (Box-folder 38: 3)
  - NCS joint systems planning, 1982 (Box-folder 38: 4)
  - Strategic forecast: U.S. Navy in the year 2000, 1984 (Box-folder 38: 5)
  - Arms control and strategic weapon utilities, 1968 (Box-folder 38: 6)
  - Research on national security policy issues, 1974 (Box-folder 38: 7)
  - A civil defense research program, 1962 (Box-folder 38: 8)
  - Trends in Western Europe political, economic and defense policies, 1969 (Box-folder 38: 9)
  - Impact of ballistic missile defense on arms control prospects, 1966 (Box-folder 38: 10)
  - Soviet views of the ABM and military strategy, 1969 (Box-folder 38: 11)
  - Examination of United States goals and interests in international affairs, 1963 (Box-folder 38: 12)
  - Foreign country policies and procedures for export controls, 1984 (Box-folder 38: 13)
  - Bases for foreign country export controls, 1984 (Box-folder 38: 14)
  - Soviet long-term economic prospects, 1979 (Box-folder 38: 15)
  - International department of the CPSU (Communist Party of the Soviet Union) Central Committee, 1982 (Box-folder 38: 16)
  - Nixon doctrine in Latin America, 1971 (Box-folder 38: 17)
  - Commentary on five studies on the future of the Soviet economy, 1979 (Box-folder 38: 18)
  - From assured destruction to assured survival, 1980 (Box-folder 38: 19)
  - Strategic planning and the rate of technological progress, 1985 (Box-folder 38: 20)
  - Mobilization and commercial communications planning, 1985 (Box-folder 38: 21)
  - Water, sewerage, and storm drainage systems, 1969 (Box-folder 39: 1)
  - Safeguard ballistic missile defense proposal, 1969 (Box-folder 39: 2)
  - Strategic interactions, 1969 (Box-folder 39: 3)
  - Framework for national communications system strategic planning, 1981 (Box-folder 39: 4)
  - Nuclear emergency operations plan, 1970 (Box-folder 39: 5)
  - Review of the U.S.-Italy cooperative science program, 1984 (Box-folder 39: 6)
  - United States unilateral arms control measures, 1961 (Box-folder 39: 7)
  - World economy and international economic cooperation, 1974 (Box-folder 39: 8)
  - Utilization of existing shelter in metropolitan areas, 1965 (Box-folder 39: 9)
  - On the nature of R&D (Research and Development) resource allocation in a democratic society, 1962 (Box-folder 39: 10)
  - Method for calculating the maximum residual dose, 1966 (Box-folder 39: 11)
  - International terrorism, 1986 (Box-folder 39: 12)
  - Periphery states of the Saudi Arabian peninsula, 1969 (Box-folder 39: 13)
  - Availability and utilization of NFSS shelter, 1965 (Box-folder 39: 14)
- Speeches and writings, 1932-1990
  - The Forgotten Roots of American Diplomacy, 1946-1990
    - Research materials, 1946-1989
      - Puritan roots, 1953-1987 (Box-folder 40: 1-9)
      - Republican roots, 1972-1988 (Box-folder 40: 10)
      - Enlightenment roots, 1946-1988 (Box-folder 41: 1-3)
      - American Revolution, 1981-1987 (Box-folder 41: 4-6)
      - American Civil War, 1976-1985 (Box-folder 41: 7-9)
      - World War II and Cold War, 1951-1988 (Box-folder 42: 1-9)
      - Nuclear strategy, 1968-1988 (Box-folder 43: 1-9)
      - Nuclear strategy, 1973-1988 (Box-folder 44: 1-8)
      - Political warfare, terrorism, and drug war, 1977-1987 (Box-folder 45: 1-9)
      - Political warfare, terrrorism, and drug war, 1980-1989 (Box-folder 46: 1-7)
      - Maritime strategy, 1983-1987 (Box-folder 47: 1-10)
      - Conclusion, 1960-1988 (Box-folder 48: 1-10)
      - Conclusion, 1974-1988 (Box-folder 49: 1-10)
    - Drafts, 1984-1990
      - First draft, 1984 (Box-folder 50: 1-11)
      - Second draft, 1986 (Box-folder 51: 1)
      - Third draft, 1987 (Box-folder 51: 2)
      - Fourth draft, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 52: 1-3)
      - Fifth draft, 1988 (Box-folder 52: 4-5)
      - Sixth draft, 1990 (Box-folder 53: 1-11)
  - US/Soviet Strategic Interaction, 1932-1987
    - Research materials, 1932-1986 (Box-folder 54: 1-8)
    - Draft, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 54: 9-12)
- Academic career file, 1981-1992
  - Lectures, 1982-1992
    - 1982 (Box-folder 55: 1)
    - 1983 (Box-folder 55: 2)
    - 1985 (Box-folder 55: 3-8)
    - 1987 (Box-folder 55: 9)
    - 1988 (Box-folder 55: 10-16)
    - 1988 (Box-folder 56: 1-2)
    - 1989 (Box-folder 56: 3)
    - 1992 (Box-folder 56: 4-10)
  - Student papers, 1981-1989
    - 1981 (Box-folder 56: 11)
    - 1983 (Box-folder 56: 12-14)
    - 1984 (Box-folder 56: 15-16)
    - 1985 (Box-folder 57: 1-2)
    - 1987 (Box-folder 57: 3-4)
    - 1988 (Box-folder 57: 5-8)
    - 1989 (Box-folder 57: 9-15)
- Writings by others, 1970-1998
  - Carpenter, William H., 1995 (Box-folder 58: 1)
  - Cohen, S. T. and William R. Van Cleave, 1976 (Box-folder 58: 2)
  - Griffith, William E., 1974 (Box-folder 58: 3)
  - Joyal, Paul M., 1984 (Box-folder 58: 4)
  - Lord, Carnes, 1979-1998 (Box-folder 58: 5-9)
  - Nurthen, William A., 1980 (Box-folder 58: 10)
  - Rimanelli, Marco, 1992 (Box-folder 58: 11)
  - Rood, H. W., 1970 (Box-folder 58: 12)
  - Rothrock, John, 1992-1995 (Box-folder 59: 1)
  - Woodall, Stephen R., 1984 (Box-folder 59: 2)
- Freedom House file, 1986-1993
  - Articles relating to human rights issues, 1986-1991 (Box-folder 59: 3)
  - Bulletins and newsletters, 1986-1991 (Box-folder 59: 4)
  - Correspondence, 1986-1993 (Box-folder 59: 5)
  - Minutes of meetings, 1987-1993 (Box-folder 59: 6-7)
  - Reports, 1991 (Box-folder 59: 8-10)
  - Surveys, 1991 (Box-folder 59: 11)
- Printed matter, 1951-1993
  - Articles and excerpts of monographs, 1951-1993
    - 1951-1953 (Box-folder 60: 1)
    - 1954-1956 (Box-folder 60: 2)
    - 1958-1963 (Box-folder 60: 3)
    - 1970-1972 (Box-folder 60: 4)
    - 1973 (Box-folder 60: 5-6)
    - 1975-1976 (Box-folder 60: 7)
    - 1976 (Box-folder 60: 8)
    - 1977 (Box-folder 60: 9)
    - 1978 (Box-folder 60: 10-11)
    - 1979 (Box-folder 60: 12)
    - 1980 (Box-folder 60: 13-14)
    - 1981 (Box-folder 61: 1-2)
    - 1982 (Box-folder 61: 3)
    - 1983 (Box-folder 61: 4-6)
    - 1984 (Box-folder 61: 7-8)
    - 1985 (Box-folder 61: 9)
    - 1986 (Box-folder 61: 10)
    - 1987 (Box-folder 61: 11)
    - 1988 (Box-folder 61: 12-13)
    - 1989 (Box-folder 61: 14)
    - 1992-1993 (Box-folder 61: 15)
  - Monographs, 1956-1983
    - 1956 (Box-folder 62: 1)
    - 1962 (Box-folder 62: 2-4)
    - 1965 (Box-folder 63: 1)
    - 1967 (Box-folder 63: 2)
    - 1972 (Box-folder 63: 3)
    - 1981 (Box-folder 63: 4-5)
    - 1982 (Box-folder 63: 6)
    - 1983 (Box-folder 63: 7)
    - 1983 (Box-folder 64: 1-2)
- Stanford Research Institute and SRI International reports, 1960-1986
  - Workshop on education and utilization of scientific and technical manpower, 1981 (Box-folder 64: 3-4)
  - Northeast Asian security, 1977 (Box-folder 64: 5)
  - Military problems of modern warfare, 1973 (Box-folder 65: 1)
  - Soviet foreign policy and the collapse of communist unity, 1971 (Box-folder 65: 2)
  - Symposium on Northeast Asia security, 1977 (Box-folder 65: 3-9)
  - Introduction to programs OPSTRA3 and OPSTRA5, 1971 (Box-folder 65: 10)
  - Description of program OPSTRAS, 1971 (Box-folder 65: 11)
  - Sub-program HARDAT, 1971 (Box-folder 65: 12)
  - Denial strategy, 1971 (Box-folder 65: 13)
  - Analysis of sufficiency criteria, 1971 (Box-folder 65: 14)
  - Uses and limitations of strategic systems effectiveness evaluation models, 1971 (Box-folder 65: 15-16)
  - Alternative Soviet foreign policies, 1971 (Box-folder 66: 1)
  - Soviet-American interactions, 1971 (Box-folder 66: 2)
  - Theoretical aspects of comparing economic capacity, 1972 (Box-folder 66: 3)
  - USSR expenditures for national security programs, 1971 (Box-folder 66: 4)
  - U.S. gross national product, 1972 (Box-folder 66: 5)
  - Comparison of U.S./USSR GNP, 1972 (Box-folder 66: 6)
  - Ruble/dollar conversion ration survey, 1972 (Box-folder 66: 7)
  - Overview of the methodology for force posture research, 1971 (Box-folder 66: 8)
  - U.S. industry support for applied R&D realted to national security, 1972 (Box-folder 66: 9)
  - Analysis of selected U.S. strategic force modifiers, 1972 (Box-folder 66: 10)
  - Selections from the Soviet military press, 1973 (Box-folder 66: 11)
  - Integrated global force posture, 1973 (Box-folder 66: 12)
  - Dynamic interaction model of the Nixon doctrine, 1973 (Box-folder 67: 1)
  - War termination concepts, 1973 (Box-folder 67: 2)
  - Theater force posture analysis, 1972 (Box-folder 67: 3)
  - Input substudies, 1972 (Box-folder 67: 4)
  - Overview of the citizen-army concept, 1972 (Box-folder 67: 5)
  - Yugoslav concept of general people's defense, 1972 (Box-folder 67: 6)
  - Communist China's trade patterns, 1974 (Box-folder 67: 7)
  - Projecting USSR economic growth, 1970 (Box-folder 67: 8)
  - Economic impact of rapid expansion of military programs, 1970 (Box-folder 67: 9)
  - Potential GNP and government expenditures in the U.S. economy, 1970 (Box-folder 67: 10)
  - Quadratic programming, 1970 (Box-folder 67: 11)
  - Long term strategic forecast for the Republic of China, 1980 (Box-folder 68: 1)
  - International terrorism, 1986 (Box-folder 68: 2)
  - U.S. security interests and options in Central Africa, 1977 (Box-folder 68: 3)
  - U.S. strategy in Northeast Asia, 1978 (Box-folder 68: 4)
  - Strategic coercion, 1984 (Box-folder 68: 5)
  - Preliminary appraisal of NS/EP, 1982 (Box-folder 68: 6)
  - National security trends and AT&T alternatives, 1982 (Box-folder 68: 7-8)
  - Financing research and development, 1981 (Box-folder 68: 9)
  - Soviet concept of the correlation of forces, 1976 (Box-folder 69: 1)
  - War termination concepts and political, economic and military targeting, 1978 (Box-folder 69: 2)
  - Significant primary fires from nuclear detonations, 1966 (Box-folder 69: 3)
  - U.S.-USSR agreement on cooperation in the fields of science and technology, 1984 (Box-folder 69: 4)
  - Soviet construction sector, 1978 (Box-folder 69: 5)
  - Boundary conditions of the Sino-Indian conflict, 1963 (Box-folder 69: 6)
  - Introduction to radiological defense planning, 1965 (Box-folder 69: 7)
  - World War II German fire document translations, 1967 (Box-folder 69: 8)
  - LOTADS scenarios, 1972 (Box-folder 70: 1)
  - Program OPSTRA2, 1969 (Box-folder 70: 2)
  - Protection against standoff thermal attacks, 1967 (Box-folder 70: 3)
  - Production and allocation of hardware, 1968 (Box-folder 70: 4)
  - Sensitivity of damage estimates for small yield weapons, 1969 (Box-folder 70: 5)
  - National vulnerabilities affecting postattack recovery, 1969 (Box-folder 70: 6)
  - Quest for a preferred U.S. nuclear war deterrence strategy, 1969 (Box-folder 70: 7)
  - Communist takeover strategies, 1977 (Box-folder 70: 8)
  - Strategic forecast: U.S. Navy in the year 2000, 1983 (Box-folder 70: 9)
  - Evaluation of chemical warfare policy alternatives, 1977 (Box-folder 71: 1-2)
  - Civil emergency preparedness, 1978 (Box-folder 71: 3)
  - Evaluation of chemical warfare policy alternatives, 1977 (Box-folder 71: 4)
  - Price indexes for Soviet 18-sector, 1978 (Box-folder 71: 5)
  - Initial testing of a disequilibrium adjustment mechanism, 1978 (Box-folder 71: 6)
  - Basic telecommunications issues affecting U.S. national security, 1980 (Box-folder 71: 7)
  - Review of national security, 1981 (Box-folder 71: 8)
  - National telecommunications policy, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 72: 1-6)
  - Effects of nuclear attacks on the petroleum industry, 1960 (Box-folder 72: 7)
  - Great power interests and conflicting objectives, 1974 (Box-folder 73: 1-2)
  - Analytical framework for assessing combat service support, 1974 (Box-folder 73: 3)
  - Expanded U.S.-Japanese security for the 1980s, 1981 (Box-folder 73: 4)
  - Maintenance of U.S. forces in Korea, 1975 (Box-folder 73: 5)
  - Soviet opportunities in the Third World, 1976 (Box-folder 73: 6)
  - Study of possible Soviet strategy of controlled conflict, 1975 (Box-folder 73: 7)
  - Issues and alternative organization and management structures, 1981 (Box-folder 73: 8)
  - Citizen-army concept in Germany, 1973 (Box-folder 74: 2)
  - Role of military force in the new international milieu, 1973 (Box-folder 74: 3)
  - European economic integration, 1973 (Box-folder 74: 4)
  - Integrated global force posture analysis, 1973 (Box-folder 74: 5)
  - Brief analysis of national security and emergency preparedness, 1981 (Box-folder 74: 6)
  - U.S. telecommunications in the 1980s, 1982 (Box-folder 74: 7-8)
  - Emerging impact of foreign competition on national security, 1982 (Box-folder 74: 9)
  - Origin of the AT&T national defense policy, 1982 (Box-folder 74: 10)
  - Analysis of press articles on the SSC colloquium, 1973 (Box-folder 75: 1)
  - Politico-military utility of Soviet CD/CEP strategic defense systems, 1979 (Box-folder 75: 2)
  - Soviet concept of national entity survival, 1978 (Box-folder 75: 3)
  - Review of the U.S.-USSR joint working group, 1981 (Box-folder 75: 4)
  - Summary report on the educational systems of the United States and the Soviet Union, 1980 (Box-folder 75: 5)
  - Soviet options, 1978 (Box-folder 75: 6-7)
  - Development of analytical systems, 1980 (Box-folder 75: 8)
  - Workshop on the strategic significance of preparedness, 1979 (Box-folder 75: 9)
  - Survival, reconstitution and recovery, 1980 (Box-folder 75: 10)
  - Basic issues connected with national command, control, and communications, 1981 (Box-folder 76: 1)
  - Substance of comparative strategy, 1978 (Box-folder 76: 2)
  - Problems and opportunities in U.S./USSR relations, 1973 (Box-folder 76: 3)
  - Trip report to the Soviet Union, 1973 (Box-folder 76: 4)
  - Emergence of a European defense research institute, 1974 (Box-folder 76: 5)
  - Transfer of advanced technology to the Soviet Union, 1974 (Box-folder 76: 6)
  - Economics and national security interactions, 1974 (Box-folder 76: 7)